{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is Tony Soprano's wife's name?",
      "choices": [
        "Angie",
        "Carmela",
        "Meadow",
        "Janice"
      ],
      "answer": "Carmela"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Tony Soprano's boat?",
      "choices": [
        "The Stugots",
        "The Livin' Da Vida Loca",
        "The Downtowner",
        "The Whitecaps"
      ],
      "answer": "The Stugots"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of business is Satriale's?",
      "choices": [
        "Restaurant",
        "Florist",
        "Laundromat",
        "Butcher shop"
      ],
      "answer": "Butcher shop"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Tony's therapist?",
      "choices": [
        "Dr. Melfi",
        "Dr. Finkelstein",
        "Dr. Rosenrosen",
        "Dr. Katz"
      ],
      "answer": "Dr. Melfi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Tony's uncle who was the boss before him?",
      "choices": [
        "Junior",
        "Mikey",
        "Pussy",
        "Richie"
      ],
      "answer": "Junior"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Tony's childhood friend who becomes a priest?",
      "choices": [
        "Bobby",
        "Paulie",
        "Christopher",
        "Father Phil"
      ],
      "answer": "Father Phil"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the mobster who is killed by Paulie in the Pine Barrens?",
      "choices": [
        "Feech",
        "Ralph",
        "Benny",
        "Vito"
      ],
      "answer": "Ralph"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Tony's mother?",
      "choices": [
        "Livia",
        "Gloria",
        "Camilla",
        "Janice"
      ],
      "answer": "Livia"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the Jewish psychiatrist that Chris sees?",
      "choices": [
        "Dr. Katz",
        "Dr. Goldstein",
        "Dr. Finkelstein",
        "Dr. Rosenrosen"
      ],
      "answer": "Dr. Finkelstein"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the strip club owned by Silvio?",
      "choices": [
        "The Bing",
        "The Spearmint Rhino",
        "The Lollipop Lounge",
        "The Crazy Horse"
      ],
      "answer": "The Bing"
    }
  ]
}
